# STEVEN ABUAN

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER

# CAREER OBJECTIVE

"Looking forward to an entry-level web developer position in an organization with good growth prospects. I'm a quick learner and very keen on details. I have a 4-month hands-on experience in a web development boot camp, which allows me to create a fully functional website and web apps."

### CERTIFICATION

KODEGO BOOTCAMP ALUMNI

Completed 16-weeks hands-on, front-end web development bootcamp

### TECHNOLOGIES I USE

- React JS
- Material UI
- CSS3

- Vue Js
- Bootstrap5
- HTML5

- Node Js
- Javascript

## EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

DATA ANNOTATOR

Glimmertech

July, 2020 - January 2022

• 2D and 3D Image Annotation

CSR / CHAT SUPPORT

TELUS International Philippines 5/F Market! Market! Mall, Taguig, 1634

January, 2019- March, 2020

- Chat support
- Handles billing queries
- Email support
- Basic technical support

#### DATA VERIFICATION ANALYST

Webscene Business Solutions Inc.

Unit G1 Vista Fino Bldg, 113 Diego Silang Ave. orner P. Dagohoy St.

December, 2017 - November, 2018

• Data verification

- +63 9613405567
- $\bigvee$

stevenjosephabuan@gmail.com

9

Signal Vill., Taguig City

https://stevenabuanportfolio.netlify.app

# OTHER TOOLS/ TECHNOLOGIES

- GIT
- GitHub
- Figma
- Mongo DB
- Firebase

## SOFT SKILL

- Web Design
- Creative Design Thinking
- Wireframe Creation
- Problem-Solving
- Visual Thinking
- Strong Communication

# EDUCATION

BS IN ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING (5TH YEAR)

Polytechnic University of the Philippines 2012-2017

#### SEMINARS ATTENDED

Guidance Counseling Seminar Personal and Social Etiquette August, 2015